no man anything but to love one
another for he that loveth another hath
fulfilled the
[Music]
law but lay up for yourselves Treasures
in Heaven for where your treasure is
there will your heart be
[Music]
also
[Applause]
amen
I want to welcome every one of
you uh to today's service today's
message is entitled
investing and how to avoid bankruptcy in
the last days uh let me see that one in
the chat if you are ready to get into
the word of God
today um I believe that God has a very
important message for us I know that it
may seem out of of character what
pastor's talking about finances yes I'm
talking about finances I'm talking about
how to invest I'm talking about how
really how to get
rich how to get rich don't tune
out don't don't think what is Pastor
doing today what what how to get rich
yes how to get rich let's let's pray and
let's get into the word of God today
heavenly
father bless us
Lord as
we
study the
importance of financial
strategies how to be
rich Lord
please guide us today in our study we
pray it in Jesus name amen
amen
um I believe believe that as Christians
we ought to be the head and not the
tale I believe that the subject of
investing is crucial for Christians
especially in the times that we are
living
in investing is important
because investing
in a sense secures our
future uh investing helps us to look
ahead to plan ahead and be prepared for
the the the the the trials you know that
that that come in the future and we're
living in a world of
uncertainty um we're living in a world
where where where you don't know what's
coming the next day and so I believe
that that as Christians again we ought
to be investing we ought to know how to
invest in order to secure for ourselves
the best possible future and so we're
going to be looking at four things today
notice with me on the
screen uh uh again investing and how to
avoid bankruptcy in the last day I want
you to note these are the four things
that I want to talk to you about today
number one why Christians must learn the
importance of
investing number two how to invest for
the greatest gains number three
diversifying your Investment
Portfolio and number four how to avoid
or the importance of avoiding worthless
stocks
these are the things that we're going to
be addressing today and I want you to
note with me uh that the Bible actually
speaks to this subject in the Book of
Proverbs Chapter 6 beginning with verse
6 the Bible says here go to the ant thou
sluggard consider her ways and be wise
put that word in the chat for me please
wise
wise go to the ant thou sluggard
consider her ways and be wise which have
no guide overseer or
ruler provideth her meat in the summer
and gathereth her food in the
Harvest I want you to understand that
the Bible here refers us to the ant who
in a sense invests in a sense
understands the importance of of
working now to together in the
summertime so that when the winter time
comes when the rainy day comes when the
emergency comes they have enough set
aside to
survive times of
trouble and so basically the text says
there are two groups of people people
there are the
sluggards and then there are the
wise there are those who understand the
importance of
investing when things are
good so that when hard times come they
have enough finances to be able to live
off
of to be able to
survive and
so this helps us to understand the
importance of investing investing is
securing your
future so that when a hard times
come you're not
bankrupt there is a a a a a a story in
the New Testament that I want to use to
illustrate the importance of investing
come with me to
Matthew Matthew chapter
25 and we're going to begin reading from
verse 1 Matthew
25 verse one the Bible
says then shall the Kingdom of Heaven be
likened unto 10 virgins which took their
lamps and went forth to meet the
bridegroom and five of them were what
everyone put the word in the chat for me
please five of them were
wise five of them were wise what can
that word tell us about the five wise
virgins it can tell us that these wise
virgins must have done something what
must they have
done they must have
invested for their future the Bible
calls them
wise they must have invested or set
aside or or or worked to
provide when times were
good so that in time of
Crisis they would not be found
bankrupt five were WI let's keep reading
and five were foolish we might say that
five were
sluggards let's keep
going the next verse the Bible says they
that were foolish took their lamps and
took no oil with
them but the wise took oil in their
vessels with their
lamps while the bridegroom tarried they
all slumbered and slept and at midnight
there was a cry made behold the
bridegroom cometh go ye out to meet him
then all those virgins arose and trimmed
their lamps and the foolish said unto
the wise give us of your oil for our
lamps are gone
out but the wise said not so lest there
be not enough for us and you but go ye
rather to them that sell and buy for
yourselves and while they went to buy
the bridegroom came and they that were
ready went in with him to the marriage
and the door was shut afterward came
also the other virgin saying Lord Lord
open to us but he answered and said
verily I say unto you I know you not
watch therefore for you know neither the
day nor the hour that the son of man
cometh what I want you to understand
here beloved is very
simple the foolish did not invest in
their future the wise invested and
that's why they had enough oil for a
time of
Crisis and beloved I want you to
understand this is so important this is
so important yes yes yes you probably
thought that I was going I know you
didn't think so for those of you who
know me I know you didn't think that I
was going to stand here today and talk
to you about how to invest in Earthly
money you knew that
right you
understand I cannot express to you
enough how important it is beloved to be
invested in your heavenly
future you got to understand beloved
that the reason that so many of us are
unprepared for crisis that we face on a
daily basis a crisis that we will face
in the future is because we haven't
learned how to invest we're not good
with investment we're not good spirit
spiritually
financially note with me what the Bible
says here in James 2:5 hearken my
beloved Brethren has not God chosen the
poor of this world rich in faith and HS
of the Kingdom which he has promised to
them that love him so I want you to note
with me that God desires us to be rich
in
faith this is is absolutely Cru crucial
beloved in order to be rich in faith we
have to learn how to invest in
faith in order to be rich in faith we
must learn how to invest in
faith hey how' you get rich in Bitcoin I
invested in Bitcoin hey how' you get
rich in Gold I invested in Gold hey how'
you get rich in faith I invested in
faith we must learn how to invest
responsibly God desires us to be rich in
faith why why come with me once again to
1 John 3:5 or chapter 5:4 which says
this for whatsoever is born of God
overcometh the world and this is the
victory that overcometh the world even
our faith so please note with
me that it is
it is our
faith that
overcomes the world that's why God
desires us to be rich in faith so that
we have enough
financially to weather rainy
days so that we have enough financially
to weather those emergencies when I find
myself in an emergency I can simply dip
into my bank of faith and take out
enough to cover the
trial the problem for many of us is that
because we have not been investing in
faith when a trial comes we don't have
it we open our faith wall and it's like
man I got nothing in there that can help
me to make it through this trial I have
I'm bankrupt I'm
broke many of us end up broke because we
don't know how to invest in fact Jesus
said in Luke 18 and verse 8 Luke 18:8
the Bible says I tell
you that he will avenge them speedily
nevertheless when the son of man cometh
will he find faith on the earth oh
man Jesus is asking the question himself
when I come Faith people are going to be
so bankrupt in faith when I come it's
going to be hard to find
it and now I need you to understand yes
receive Faith reserves we need to
understand how is how can
I replenish how can I build up my faith
reserves how can I have that that that
that that influx of Faith how can I
invest so that when the rainy day comes
when the unexpected trial comes I
already have enough in the listen but
when you try to go get Faith in the
midst of a crisis H come on let me let
me let
me let me let me let me slow down let me
slow down I I need to build this thing
carefully the first thing we we
understand thus far is the importance of
investing why because those who do not
invest ahead of time will find
themselves in crisis when the trial
comes whether that trial is the End Time
Crisis that everybody knows is coming or
it's your own
crisis your own little time of trouble
your own big time of trouble your own
personal crisis beloved if you do not if
you do not have enough faith if you have
not been investing you will not have
enough there will be nothing to tap into
Clint if it's not
there so then the question now becomes
the question now becomes H H uh how can
I how can I create how can I build my
emergency
fund my rainy day fund so that as I'm
walking through life I know that
whatever comes my way I will be rich
enough to deal with it how many of you
would like to be rich put a one in the
chat if you would like to be rich I want
to be rich I would love I I I desire
with everything I have to be
rich in
faith put that one in the
chat if you would like to be a faith
billionaire put that one in the chat if
you would like to be a faith billionaire
yeah I want to be a faith billionaire
beloved I want to have enough Faith to
take me through any trial that I can
possibly fa face I want to have enough
Faith where I can dip into that Faith
while and go oh what okay boom I got
enough to cover it I got enough to cover
it that beloved is what God is God
desires us to be rich so the question
then is how do I learn how to invest in
order to get the greatest gains all
right come on let's go let's go let's go
back to the screen the key to Investing
For the greatest gains what is the key
to Investing For the greatest gains the
key beloved
is to buy
low let let let me repeat that let me
repeat that the key beloved is to
buy
low did y'all hear what I just said put
that one in the chat if you understand
what I mean when I say Buy Low you want
to buy that thing when it is at its
lowest price you want to buy that thing
at a low price you buy low
so the question is how do we buy loow
notice with me the book of Isaiah 55
verse 1 the Bible sayso everyone that
thirsteth Come Ye to the waters and he
that has no money Come Ye
byy and eat yay come buy wine and milk
without money and without price I need
y'all to understand something beloved
this is why this is so amazing because
in order to get what we need it
costs it is a free
gift
wow Jesus says listen you know when you
talk to people about investing they
always want to ask well how much money
do you have and what do you have that
you can put down but Jesus says you
don't need any money with me because
this is a free gift that I have given to
you so come you don't need money you're
buying low and the Beautiful Thing
beloved about buying low buying this
gift of Salvation which cost us nothing
is that that faith and that gift
Everything Jesus gives to us its value
is already way above what you paid for
it which is
nothing so in some cases you buy
something low and you're waiting for the
value of that thing to go up before you
sell but with this you never need to
sell because what you bought at a low
cost is already as much as it will ever
be worth which is more than you could
ever ever ever
imagine you are buying low but the value
of it is already infinitely more than
you can
imagine so so you buy
low the value is already Priceless but
it doesn't stop there you see in this
parable of the the five wise virgins and
the five foolish virgins five are wise
five are foolish five invested I want
you to know the parable ends in verse 13
it's Matthew 25 verse 1 to verse 13 but
notice what happens in the very next
verse Jesus moves to a second Parable
and notice this Parable Matthew 2:14 the
Bible says Matthew
25:14 um for the Kingdom of Heaven is
liken unto a man traveling into a far
country who called his own servants and
delivered unto them his
goods and unto
one he gave five talents and to another
two and to another one to every man
according to his several ability and
straight way he took his journey now
notice verse 16 then he that had
received the five talents went and what
did he do everyone put it in the chat
for me what did he do with the five
talents the money that was given
him put the word in the chat for me
please what did he do do with the money
yes yes yes yes brother Robert yes Patty
yes yes Ashante yes Veronica yes Darlene
yes Jamie yes Richard yes the prodigal
yes Lynette he traded so now watch this
when we come to Jesus broke cuz we don't
have anything he says buy of me buy of
me you don't need money just buy of me
and when we buy of him we become his
servants and now as his servants here's
what Jesus does he says I'm G to give
you
money I'm GNA give you
money and what I want you to do with
that money is I want you to trade it I
want you to invest this and produce
more are y'all following me so you buy
low you get money in your pocket wow
what what kind of deal is it I buy low I
get this money in my pocket that's not
mine and then I get to trade on
it I get to trade on
it oh man please y'all listen to this
listen to this I get to buy more he says
I look trade and I want you to keep
buying I want you to keep I want you to
buy up as much as you can so how do we
buy up as much as we we can we keep
going back to the
seller who is the
seller it's Jesus he tells us right
there in Revelation 13:18 Revelation
3:18 I counsel thee to buy of me beloved
Jesus is the one that is
selling so he says come and I want you
to buy of me and I want you to keep
buying of me I want you to keep
rededicating yourself to me I want you
to keep asking of me I want you to keep
pring of me keep buying keep buying keep
buying because the time is coming where
no man listen to me y'all the time is
coming where no man will be able to buy
or sell not only in the physical world
beloved but also in the spiritual world
I don't know if y'all caught
that the time is coming beloved where no
man will be able to buy or sell not only
in the physical world but also in the
spiritual world the time is coming where
he that is righteous will be right to
still and he that is filthy will be
filthy still beloved now is the time to
buy while prices are
low while prices are low beloved now let
me tell you it is not impossible to buy
in times of trouble it's just that
buying in time of trouble becomes more
expensive see we want to buy
Faith now when when when things are are
not so bad in our
lives it's when we try to initiate faith
when we try to buy faith in the midst of
a crisis that we recognize and we
realize how expensive Faith Can
Be You See the book of Ephesians chapter
4:13 tells us it tells us this it says
till we all come in the unity of the
faith and of the knowledge of the Son of
God unto a perfect man unto the measure
and the stature of the fullness of
Christ what I need you to understand
beloved is that the unity of Faith here
being spoken of which leads us to become
a perfect man that word for perfect
means
mature what the text is telling us is
that our faith must be mature meaning
faith
grows Faith takes time to mature we
might call it longterm
maturity long-term maturity beloved
trying to buy faith in the midst of a
crisis is is detrimental because you
haven't had time to know how to use
it when you by faith when when when
times are not so rough when you by faith
when the cost is low when you buy faith
when when when when things around you
are are not so bad you can get to learn
how to use that faith and practice and
okay H I'm going to have faith today
that I'm not going to get mad at my
neighbor I'm going to have faith today
that I'm not little things you can begin
to exercise that Faith because you've
bought it I bought it now I want to use
it how do I use this thing that I just
bought but when you don't when you just
skip faith for days and for weeks and
for months and for years and then a is
hits and now you're trying to exercise
Faith
beloved come on come on Note with me
note with me the the the counsel given
us in re in in Jeremiah 12:5 the Bible
says if thou Hast run with the footmen
and they have wearied thee then how can
you contend with horses and if in the
land of Peace wherein you trusted they
wearied thee they wore you out then how
will you do in the swelling of the
Jordan the question is if you hav't
exercise faith if you haven't exercise
uh uh love if you haven't exercised
commitment when things are not so bad
how are you going to do when the trial
really hits how are you going to do when
that rainy day comes how are you going
to do when that unexpected challenge
comes how are you going to manage if you
weren't even able to manage in the Small
Things the Bible
says in Amos chter
8 and verse 11 behold the days come
sayith the Lord God that I will send a
famine in the land not a famine of bread
nor thirst for water but of hearing the
words of the Lord and they shall Wander
from sea to Sea and from the north even
to the east they shall run to and fro to
seek the word of the Lord and shall not
find it a famine is in fact coming and
beloved in order for us to be wise we
ought to consider the ant and begin to
prare to stock up remember
Joseph who stocked up on the bread
because he knew that a famine was
coming you see Beloved the five wise
virgins invested in a long-term Faith
strategy which produces greater yields
because there are greater risks but the
foolish virgins opted for shortterm
Investments which were less risky but
they didn't have because they didn't
have much to lose but there was not much
to gain
either we need to learn how to invest
beloved in a faith that will not fail so
that when crisis hits we have enough
money to cover the
crisis we have enough Faith to cover the
crisis so come on let's break this down
then let's break this down and how do we
get to this place how do we get to this
place where where we have enough in the
faith Bank to cover our crisis to cover
our times of trouble
well every Christian should have a good
Investment Portfolio in other words you
should diversify invest in more than one
thing not just one thing are y'all
catching
me come on come back to the screen are
y'all catching this your your portfolio
is is the range of things that you have
invested in and they always say don't
put your eggs in one basket right you
got to invest across multiple platforms
you got to invest in multiple things so
then my question is your question might
be all right Pastor well well I want to
be
rich I want to be rich in faith yes
beloved I love that prodigal Jesus is
our financial advisor and and as our
financial advisor he has already told us
what we should invest in and I want to
suggest beloved that there are six uh
six commod six things we need to invest
in if we want to be rich and well
prepared for what is coming ahead
whether it is the end time or whe is
whether it is our own personal crisis if
I can invest in these six things in
these six stocks then I will be all
right I will be rich enough to handle
whatever the devil brings my way what
are those six things come on let's go
let's go first invest beloved invest in
gold invest in
gold invest y'all put it in the chat
invest in
gold the Bible says in 1 Peter chapter 1
verse6 wherein you greatly Rejoice
though now for a season if need be you
are in heaviness through manifold
temptations that the trial of your faith
being much more precious than of gold
that perisheth though it be tried with
fire might be found unto praise and
honor and Glory at the appearing of
Jesus Christ invest in gold beloved
invest in faith ask the
Lord
Lord Give Me
Faith help me to to to to gather enough
faith that I will have enough for an
emergency fund I will have enough for
things that I'm going through today or
tomorrow or the next day but Lord help
me to be
rich in
Gold help me to invest in faith because
I know that it is by faith that I
overcome the world it is by faith that I
overcome the dragon so teach me Lord how
to invest in gold how to invest in faith
how to invest in in in that thing that
help me to see kind of like the
Candlestick how the Candlestick was the
light that enables one to you can't see
in darkness you can seeing light and and
so the Candlestick the light of that
Candlestick which which which which
burned in the sanctuary allows us to see
by faith that which our literal eyes
cannot see at the moment Lord teach me
how to see lighten my eyes that I may
see help me Lord to be rich in faith not
only should I invest in Gold not only
should you invest in gold beloved but I
also want to say that you should invest
in
silver you should invest in silver
beloved no question about it silver is a
hot commod you need to invest in silver
the Bible says the words of the Lord are
pure words as silver tried in a furnace
of Earth purified seven times so beloved
listen to me we need to invest in the
word of God the Bible says
study
study study to show thyself approved
unto God a Workman that needeth not to
be ashamed rightly dividing the word of
truth how do I invest in the word by
spending time in the word how do I
invest in faith by spending time in
Faith Lord help me to invest in gold
help me to invest in silver help me to
set time aside beloved listen to me if
you're going to invest in something
spiritual you have to put the time in
and most of the reason why many of us
are bankrupt and don't even realize it
is because we haven't put the time in we
haven't put the time into the word to be
rich in the word we haven't put the time
in in faith to be rich in faith God says
listen if you're not willing to invest
time time beloved is the greatest
commodity time beloved is the greatest
asset you have and if you are not
willing to invest time in prayer if
you're not willing to invest time in
study listen to me you are going to be
poor in all these
things what else should we invest in
what are these six Commodities not only
should we invest in in in in faith the
seven Branch Candlestick gold not only
should we invest in silver the word of
God the table of showbread we beloved we
must also invest in oil yes yes yes
beloved invest in oil the five wise
virgins invested in oil that we know for
sure invest in oil what do you mean oil
Pastor how is oil a hot commodity how is
oil so important to us listen Psalm
45 and verse
S thou lovest righteousness and hatest
wickedness therefore God thy God has
anointed Ed thee with the oil of
gladness above thy fellows I need you to
understand that oil is a symbol of the
Holy Spirit the spirit of the Lord is
upon me because he has anointed me to
preach the gospel this is Jesus speaking
of the oil that was poured out upon Him
spiritually representing the spirit of
God being poured upon him and even Acts
chapter 10:38 says how God anointed
Jesus of Nazareth with the Holy Ghost
invest in oil
beloved you better invest in gold you
better invest in silver you better
invest in oil not only beloved this is
going to sound really like what but
that's so plenteous invest in
water invest in
water first John first John chapter 1
verse
9 and it may not be in my notes here I'm
just going to go go ahead and read 1
John 1:9 the Bible says if we confess
our sins he is faithful and just to
forgive us our sins and to cleanse us oh
I got it I got it let me come back I'm
I'm I'mma stick with my notes invest in
Wood I I I jumped ahead too quick invest
in Wood not only not only then should I
invest in gold not only should I invest
in silver not only should I invest in
oil the altar of incense but I should
also invest in
wood put that word in the chat for me
y'all put that word in the chat for me
wood
gold
silver
oil wood invest in Wood Pastor what do
you mean the Bible tells us Jesus said
If any man will come after me let him
deny himself and take up the cross take
up his cross dead
and follow me are y'all catching this
invest in Wood beloved invest in the
cross invest in that sacrifice
represented by the altar of sacrifice in
the sanctuary invest in the sacrifice of
Christ learn what it means to sacrifice
for the good of others learn what it
means to sacrifice to lay yourself on
the cross to lay yourself on the altar
so what I'm trying to tell you beloved
is that in order order to be rich in
order to be to be well-rounded to meet
End Time
Crisis to meet crisis that you will face
in your life beloved it is not it is not
good enough to be rich in one
thing oh well I'm rich in oil so I don't
need to worry about gold I don't need to
worry about silver I don't need to worry
about the wood beloved listen to me you
you have to diversify because there are
some people who are rich in silver can
break the word of God down like nothing
you have ever heard and yet beloved may
be lacking in the oil may be lacking in
the wood maybe lacking in the gold and
beloved you might know the word backward
and forward and have it memorized but if
you're not rich in Gold if you're not
rich in oil if you're not rich in Wood
it's not going to amount to
anything you must diversify not only
beloved our we to invest in Wood we are
to invest in water yes yes water it's so
plenteous I know but please understand
the Bible says if we confess our sins he
is faithful and just to forgive us our
sins and to cleanse us from all
unrighteousness that labor beloved in
the sanctuary that was used to be to to
wash and to wash away filth and to wash
away we need to learn how to invest in
that water of life we need to learn how
to invest in forgiving others we need to
learn how to
invest in being merciful we need to
learn how to invest in this purification
element of water Lord help me to be
rich in Gold rich in silver rich in oil
rich in Wood rich in water and the last
thing Beloved the last thing I need you
to understand that you must invest in is
you must invest beloved in fire
yes yes invest in fire invest in Fire
come on y'all invest in fire the Bible
says in the Song of Solomon chapter 8
set me as a seal upon thine heart and as
a seal upon thine arm for love is as
strong as death jealousy is cruel as a
grave the coals thereof are are coals of
fire which has a most veman flame many
Waters cannot quench love neither can
the floods drown it please understand
beloved that if love is is symbolized by
fire the Bible says in Romans 13:10 love
worketh no ill to his neighbor therefore
love is the fulfilling of the law
beloved these six things are the are the
six articles that are found in the
sanctuary invest in gold invest in
silver invest in oil invest in Wood
invest in water invest in Fire and
beloved listen to
me as we invest inv in these things and
become rich in the word of God rich in
faith the altar of incense or the seven
Branch Candlestick rich in oil the altar
of incense rich in water the labor rich
in fire the law of God rich in Wood the
altar of sacrifice when we learn when we
become rich in these things beloved it
doesn't matter what the devil throws our
way we will have enough in the bank to
cover it why because we have become
spiritual
billionaires we have become spiritual
tycoons who have enough we I got it I
can c not I got it but Christ got
it my my stock
broker my financial
advisor told me how to make it through
the
crisis you see beloved here is the
problem here is the
problem we need two things we need two
things in order to trade we need
time and urgency we need
time an urgency and the issue with us
beloved is
that so many of us do not take the time
to
invest we just don't take the time to
invest when the crisis
hits it is pretty much too late to start
investing people don't invest in a stock
when it's when it's high they want to
invest when it's low because oh it's too
expensive
now and what we need to understand
beloved is that those sleeping virgins
went to buy oil in in a time of Crisis
not in a time of
Peace our work beloved is to trade we
came to Christ he gave us he gave he he
said you don't need money but I'm going
to give you money okay now Lord teach me
how to trade on
this teach me how to trade on Silver so
I can multiply silver how to trade on
gold so I can multiply gold how to trade
on oil oil so I can multiply oil how I
can trade on fire so I can multiply fire
how I can trade on wood so I can
multiply wood how I can trade on water
to multiply water and the problem
beloved that many of us have is that
many of us are buying worthless
stock we're buying counterfeit gold and
we don't even realize it we're buying
counterfeit
silver we're buying fake Oil we're
buying rotten wood we're buying spoiled
or Bitter Water we're we're we're buying
these things and not even
realizing that it's on it's when the
crisis hits that many realize I don't
have the faith to endure
this I don't even I I can't I don't know
where to go in the word of God to endure
to help I don't
have we realize that what we have been
buying wasn't worth
anything they call call it a honey
pot in the investment
World it looks
sweet it looks
good many of us beloved we're buying the
wrong we're buying Comm we're buying
worthless
stock or we're trading what God has
given us for worthless
stock and so every time beloved we we go
out there and we do something stupid we
do something foolish we do something
outside the will of God we've just
traded because the devil came to us and
said hey I'll give you
this and it's not he's not giving it to
you for free when you take his thing
you've just given up some of your
stock that's what he does he's trading
it's a trading remember Satan
merchandised in heaven he was a Trader
in heaven TR a i t o r and t r a d e
r and so many of
us without understanding how the trade
Works we're trading with Satan all the
time and the more we trade with him is
the more we
lose it's the more we lose what God has
given
us
the Bible says what does it profit a man
if he gained the whole world and yet
lose his own
soul you
remember you remember that the traitor
came to Jesus in the wilderness right
you do remember that and the traitor
said to him hey I will give you the
whole
world if you do business with me if you
trade with
me Jesus is like
nah not
selling I'm not buying and I'm not
selling beloved listen to me there are
many that are bankrupt that don't even
know that they're
bankrupt and it's not until the trial
hits it is not until crisis
hits that you realize within your own
heart whether you had been preparing
whether you are rich or whether you are
poor and the thing about it beloved is
that you you won't know that until
you're in the
crisis and so beloved it behooves
us to come to the Lord and humble
ourselves and say Lord I
know I know that I'm poor please Lord
make me Rich please Lord teach me how to
trade teach me how to invest teach me
how to be prepared teach me how to set
aside that emergency fund teach me Lord
how to set aside that rainy day fund
teach me Lord how to become so rich that
when the crisis
hits I will discover
how rich I really am in
you what does it profit a
man Matthew 16:26 what is a man
profited what is a man profited if he
shall gain the whole world and lose his
own soul or what shall a man give in
exchange change for his
soul beloved I appeal to you
today start
investing start
investing read books on how to
invest the Bible yeah yeah yeah read
books how to
strengthen how to invest in faith
how to invest in the spirit of
sacrifice how to invest in the word
whatever you need to do to educate
yourself in the spiritual investment
World avoid the worthless stocks buy
this buy
that the devil will come to you with all
kinds of trait buy this hey this is
excellent
understand the importance of
investing diversify your
portfolio invest in order to make the
greatest
gains and avoid those worthless
stocks you do these
things and you will
be
rich in the Lord
Jesus Heavenly Father
I thank you Lord for
speaking I thank you
Lord for encouraging us to
invest may we be
wise like the
ant like the five wise
virgins may we invest against the
future
so that when we Face our
challenges be it small
ones or ones we thought we could never
handle may we be
found to be
rich in
you this we pray in the precious and
Holy Name of
Jesus let everyone say amen and
amen um I'm going to go ahead and put
this up on the screen uh for those of
you that would like to to join uh our
Bible studies for baptism if you're
interested in baptism please see the QR
code there scan that QR code and we will
we will connect with you if you would
like to get these slides you can do the
same uh scan the QR code you will get
the slides
um immediately after this service um we
are going to be having our second
communion service and so we invite you
to join us for that communion service um
we'll put the link in the chat and uh
we'll be doing that immediately after on
alter live and um again I want to thank
you all for joining with us
today um may
you be blessed by this message and
um May you become rich in the Lord may
you become rich in the Lord God bless
you and I will see you over on alter
live joining us today if this is your
first time worshiping with us please
check out our website at Living mana.
Church we are not just here for Sabbath
service we have weekly programming too
that covers mental health physical
health weekly prayer service Financial
Health and proving the existence of God
it is our desire that our programming
will continue to bless you please
continue to pray for us as we fulfill
God's mission to go into all the world
with the Gospel of Jesus
[Music]
Christ
e